{
    "subject": "resource/Edward_J._Robeson,_Jr.",
    "predicate": "property/almaMater",
    "object": "resource/University_of_Georgia",
    "human_readable": "Edward J. Robeson Jr.'s alma mater is the University of Georgia.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9858757853507996,
            "question": "Is Edward J. Robeson Jr. a graduate of the University of Georgia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9827983975410461,
            "question": "Did Edward J. Robeson Jr. study at the University of Georgia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9392474889755249,
            "question": "Name the university Edward J. Robeson Jr. graduated from."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9350168108940125,
            "question": "What is the name of Edward J. Robeson Jr.'s alma mater?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8650680184364319,
            "question": "What university did Edward J. Robeson Jr. attend?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8542104363441467,
            "question": "What university is associated with Edward J. Robeson Jr.'s education?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8465049266815186,
            "question": "To which university did Edward J. Robeson Jr. belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7999098896980286,
            "question": "Edward J. Robeson Jr. received his education from which institution?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7385380864143372,
            "question": "Where did Edward J. Robeson Jr. go to school?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.657764196395874,
            "question": "Which institution of higher learning educated Edward J. Robeson Jr.?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Edward J. Robeson Jr.'s alma mater is the University of Georgia.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4943_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where did Edward J. Robeson Jr. go to school?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4943_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Edward J. Robeson Jr. received his education from which institution?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4943_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=To which university did Edward J. Robeson Jr. belong?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4943_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4943_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4943_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4943_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4943_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4943_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4943_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4943_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4943_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4943_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4943_7.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have more triples you'd like me to evaluate!"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response in the requested format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that the documents mention that Edward J. Robeson Jr. attended the public schools of Quitman, Marietta, and Sparta, Ga., but his graduation from the University of Georgia is only mentioned as part of a list of jobs he held from 1910 to 1915, not as an indication of his alma mater."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents indicate that Edward John Robeson, Jr., attended and graduated from the University of Georgia in 1910, confirming that his alma mater is indeed the University of Georgia."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The claim is wrong because the text clearly states that Edward J. Robeson Jr. was graduated from the University of Georgia at Athens in 1910, but later on, another person named Paul Robeson's education history is given and it doesn't mention Edward J. Robeson Jr., and other context information also confirms that a different person named Paul Robeson attended Rutgers, which makes Edward J. Robeson Jr.'s education history inconsistent.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}